import 'package:news_updates/models/quiz_model.dart';

List<QuizQuestion> socialAffairsQuestions = [
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which organization is known for advocating for human rights globally?",
    options: ["United Nations", "World Health Organization", "International Monetary Fund", "World Bank"],
    correctAnswer: "United Nations",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the primary goal of the United Nations Sustainable Development Goals?",
    options: ["End poverty", "Promote global trade", "Increase military spending", "Expand space exploration"],
    correctAnswer: "End poverty",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which global event is celebrated annually on December 10th to honor human rights?",
    options: ["World AIDS Day", "Human Rights Day", "International Women's Day", "World Environment Day"],
    correctAnswer: "Human Rights Day",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which international agreement focuses on combating climate change?",
    options: ["Paris Agreement", "Geneva Convention", "Kyoto Protocol", "Copenhagen Accord"],
    correctAnswer: "Paris Agreement",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the name of the initiative that aims to eradicate extreme poverty worldwide by 2030?",
    options: ["Global Goals", "Millennium Development Goals", "Poverty Alleviation Initiative", "End Poverty Campaign"],
    correctAnswer: "Global Goals",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which organization provides emergency aid and long-term assistance to communities in crisis?",
    options: ["Red Cross", "Doctors Without Borders", "Amnesty International", "Greenpeace"],
    correctAnswer: "Red Cross",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What does the term 'socioeconomic status' refer to?",
    options: ["Economic and social position", "Health status", "Educational level", "Political affiliation"],
    correctAnswer: "Economic and social position",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which group is most commonly targeted for social discrimination and inequality?",
    options: ["Ethnic minorities", "Majority groups", "Government officials", "Corporate executives"],
    correctAnswer: "Ethnic minorities",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the primary focus of the International Labour Organization (ILO)?",
    options: ["Workers' rights", "Environmental protection", "Health care", "Education reform"],
    correctAnswer: "Workers' rights",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What does 'gender equality' aim to achieve?",
    options: ["Equal rights and opportunities for all genders", "Equal pay only for women", "Equal representation in politics", "Equal access to education"],
    correctAnswer: "Equal rights and opportunities for all genders",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which global movement advocates for the rights and inclusion of people with disabilities?",
    options: ["Disability Rights Movement", "Global Inclusion Initiative", "International Disability Alliance", "Special Olympics"],
    correctAnswer: "International Disability Alliance",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the term used to describe the movement of people from rural areas to cities?",
    options: ["Urbanization", "Globalization", "Industrialization", "Migration"],
    correctAnswer: "Urbanization",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which international body focuses on promoting peace and security worldwide?",
    options: ["North Atlantic Treaty Organization", "European Union", "United Nations Security Council", "World Trade Organization"],
    correctAnswer: "United Nations Security Council",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What does the term 'digital divide' refer to?",
    options: ["Gap between those with and without internet access", "Difference in digital skills", "Varied digital content quality", "Disparity in online privacy"],
    correctAnswer: "Gap between those with and without internet access",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which organization is known for its efforts in poverty reduction and development?",
    options: ["World Bank", "International Monetary Fund", "International Organization for Migration", "United Nations Development Programme"],
    correctAnswer: "United Nations Development Programme",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What does the term 'social justice' focus on?",
    options: ["Fairness and equality in society", "Economic growth", "Cultural preservation", "Technological advancement"],
    correctAnswer: "Fairness and equality in society",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which international document outlines fundamental human rights and freedoms?",
    options: ["Universal Declaration of Human Rights", "Convention on the Rights of the Child", "Geneva Conventions", "International Covenant on Civil and Political Rights"],
    correctAnswer: "Universal Declaration of Human Rights",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the main aim of the Global Fund?",
    options: ["Fight against AIDS, tuberculosis, and malaria", "Promote global trade", "Support educational initiatives", "Enhance technological innovation"],
    correctAnswer: "Fight against AIDS, tuberculosis, and malaria",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which initiative aims to provide clean water and sanitation to communities worldwide?",
    options: ["Water.org", "Global Water Partnership", "World Water Council", "Sanitation and Water for All"],
    correctAnswer: "Sanitation and Water for All",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What is the primary focus of the World Health Organization (WHO)?",
    options: ["Global health issues", "Economic development", "Environmental protection", "Educational reform"],
    correctAnswer: "Global health issues",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "Which international body monitors and promotes international labor standards?",
    options: ["International Labour Organization", "World Trade Organization", "United Nations Development Programme", "World Bank"],
    correctAnswer: "International Labour Organization",
  ),
  QuizQuestion(
    question: "What does the term 'human trafficking' refer to?",
    options: ["Illegal trade of people for exploitation", "Illegal immigration", "Smuggling of goods", "Unlawful labor practices"],
    correctAnswer: "Illegal trade of people for exploitation",
  ),
];
